NAA Additional Records 6004
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
NAA Additional Records
1936-2005
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
National Academy of Arbitrators (NAA)
6004
24.5 cubic feet
23.5 linear ft.
Records.
5757763
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, September 30, 2004
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, April 06, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5246: NAA Records 5775: NAA Records 5796: NAA Additional Records 5985: NAA Additional Files Regarding Proceedings 6004 AV: NAA Audio-Visual Material 6004 OHM: NAA History Committee Oral History Interview Masters 6004 OHT: NAA History Committee Oral History Interview Transcripts 6204: NAA Restricted Committee Files 6205: NAA Committee Files 6136: Dennis Nolan Collection of National Academy of Arbitrators History Files
Industrial relations; Arbitration, Industrial; Collective labor agreements; Mediation and conciliation, Industrial; National Academy of Arbitrators
5757763
- Annual Meeting, 1979-1981 (gaps). (Box 1)
  - Guest Expenditures 12-6-75, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Attendance - Annual Meetings, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Bibliography/ Research Com. Work Product, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Questionaire (per Nicholas Zumas) - 3/16/90, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Annual Meeting - 1979 Folder #1 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Annual Meeting - 1979 Folder #2 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Annual Meeting - 1980 Folder #1 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Annual Meeting - 1980 Folder #2 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Academy Show -- 1980 Folder #1 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Academy Show -- 1980 Folder #2 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Membership Meeting National Academy of Arbitrators, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - 34th Annual Meeting (NAA), 1981 Maui Hawaii (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - 1981 B&G + Membership Meetings (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Transcript of Ralph Seward tapes -- Maui, HI -- 5-1981 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Scope and Contents
    2 Cassettes - not found in folder(?) - 3/2015
  - Annual Meeting - Maui, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Maui 1981 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Committee for National Meeting of Arbitrators, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Sinecropi. Presidential papers. (Box 2)
  - Arrangements Committee Ottawa, Canada, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Region II - New York, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Regional Meeting 5: Atlanta, Georgia, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - NAA Region 10 Meeting, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Region 9 -- Cincinatti, Ohio, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Region 6 Meeting, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Misc. Committees, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Basic Correspondence -NAA-, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Basic Correspondence Dana E. eischen, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - The Chronicle May 1990-(Pres. Elect)May 1992 NAA, 1990-1992 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Academy History Committee May 1990(Pres. Elect)-May 1992 NAA, 1990-1992 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Continuation Legal Education, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Dues Waiver Policy Committee, 1976-1992 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Committee on Gender-Neutral terminology, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Committee Appointments (Notes), 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Program Committee 1992 Annual Meeting (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Arrangements commiittee Atlanta (May 1992 Meeting) (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Research Committee May 1990(Pres. Elect)-May 1992, 1990-1992 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Regional Education Committee May 1990(Pres. Electy)-May 1992, 1990-1992 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Public Employment Dispute Settlement Committee May 1990(Pres. Elect)-May 1992, 1990-1992 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Professional Responsibility and Grievances Committee May 1990(Pres. Elect)- May 1992, 1990-1992 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Personnel Committee (newly founded), 1992 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Membership Committee May 1990(Pres.elect)- May 1992, 1990-1992 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - New Member Orientation Committee May 1990(Pres.Elect) -May 1992, 1990-1992 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Long Range Program Planning Committee May 1990( Pres.Elect)-May 1992, 1990-1992 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Legal Representation committee May 1990(Pres. Elect)-May 1992, 1990-1992 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Legals Affair Committee May 1990(Pres. Elect)-May 1992, 1990-1992 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Law & Legislation Committee May 1990(Pres. Elect)-May 1992, 1990-1992 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - International Studies Committee May 1990(Pres. Elect)-May 1992, 1990-1992 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Honorary Memberships committee May 1990(Pres. Elect)-May 1992, 1990-1992 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Future Meeting Arrangements May 1991-May 1992, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Designating Agency Liaison comm. May 1990(Pres. Elect)-May 1992, 1990-1992 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Continuing Education Committee May 1990(Pres. Elect)-May 1992, 1990-1992 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Audit Committee May 1990(Pres. Elect)-May 1992, 1990-1992 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Academy Governance Committee May 1990(Pres. Elect)-May 1992, 1990-1992 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Annual Meeting, 1982-1984. (Box 3)
  - Annual Meeting - 1982 Folder #1 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Annual Meeting - 1982 Folder #2 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Board of governors Minutes 1982 Annual Meeting (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Financial Papers, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Arthur Malinowski Folder #1, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Arthur Malinowski Folder #2, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Minutes 5/28/83, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - 1984 Annual Meeting Hyatt-Regency Chicago, IL (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - 1984 Annual Meeting (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - NAA 1984 Annual Business Meeting (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - 1983 Annual Meeting (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - 1983 Arrangements Committee Ted Weatherill, Chairman (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Misc. - 1983 Meetings (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - 1983 Annual Meeting Committee Reports (Originals) (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - '84 Annual Meeting arrangements committee 83-84, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Committee reports, 1984-1985. (Box 4)
  - 1984-85 President John E. Dunsford, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Executive Committee 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Auditing Committee Howard Cole - 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Paper - Annual Meeting '84 Jones, Block, Mittenthal, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - 1985 Annual Meeting May 27-31 - Seattle, WA (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Committee 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Academy History James Stern - 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Academy's Role in the Development of New Arbitrators - Ben Aaron, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Con. Ed. Conf., 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Designating Agency Liaison Lewis Gill - 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Disability Insurance Ted High - 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Future Meeting Arrangements Thomas Roberts - 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Com. On Law & Legislation Emily Maloney - 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Legal Affairs Howard Block - 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Legal Representation Milton Rubin - 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Intern Training Charles Mullin - 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Legal Representation "Comments" 84-85, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Membership Committee Alfred C. Dybeck - 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - New Member Orientation Alexander Porter - 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Nominating Com., 1985 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Overseas Correspondents Charles Morris - 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Policy Handbook Martin Wagner - 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Program Committee William Murphy - 1985 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Prof. Resp. + Griev., 1985 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Publications Walter Gershenfeld - 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Continuing Education Com. Carlton Snow - 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Research Committee Mario Bognanno - 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Work Product: NAA Research Com. Berkeley,Bognanno,Jedel,Lowenberg, 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Nat'. Coor/Regional Activities James Sherman - 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Region #1 - New England Paul J. Dorr, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Region #2 - New York City Samuel Ranhand, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Region #3 - East. Pennsylvania Gladys Gershenfeld, 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Region #4 - D.C. Joseph A. Sickles, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Region #5 - Southeast Harold D. Jones, Sr., 1984 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Region #6 - Upstate New York Donald P. Goodman, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Region #7 - Canada C. Brian Williams, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Region #8 - West. Pennsylvania James Clair Duff, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Region #9 - Ohio Hyman Cohen, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Region #10 - Michigan Ruth Kahn, 1984-1986 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Region #10 - Michigan Ruth Kahn, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Region #11 - Illinois Robert Mueller, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Region #12 - St. Louis Peter J. Maniscalco, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Region #13 - Southwest Ray Britton, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Region #14 - Rocky Mountain David Goodman, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Region #15 - North. California Joe H. Henderson, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Region #16 - South. California C. Chester Brisco, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Region #17 - Pacific N.W. J.B. Gillingham, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - B/G Meeting - Nov. 7-8, 85 St. Paul, Mn, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 48)
- Annual meeting files proceedings, 1983-1987; Board of Governors Meetings, 1954,1956,1957; NAA Continuing Ed. Conference Reading Materials, 1994, 1995; Discussion guides (2 copies each); Contested election - Marvin Feldman (1 file). (Box 5)
  - 1983 Annual Meeting Quebec (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - 1984 Annual Meeting Chicago (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - National Academy of Arbitrations, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Ntional Academy of Arbitratiors, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - 1985 Annual Meeting Seattle (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - National Academy of Arbitrators, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - National Academy of Arbitrators Fortieth Annual Meeting, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Board of Governance 1950's, 1954-1956 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - NAA - 1989 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - NAA - 1995 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - NAA - 1994 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Discussion Guides, 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - NAA Subcommittee on Seminars Folder #1, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - NAA Subcommittee on Seminars Folder #2, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - NAA Seminar Folder #3, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Office correspondence and related documents, 1983-1988. (Box 7)
  - AT&T Technologies, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - AT&T Technologies, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Regional Organization Edwin Teple - Chair 83-84, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Membership Committee 83-84 Arvid Anderson, Chair, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Committee 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Officers, Board Members & Committee - 1983 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Legal Representation 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Auditing Committee Howard Cole, chair. 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Executive Com. 1983-'84, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Canadian Payments 1983 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - New Members Orientation committee Arnold M. Zack - Chairman, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Nominating Committee 83-84 James Stern - Chairman, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Overseas Correspondents Com. Charles J. Morris - Chairperson, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Professional Responsibility & Grievances Com. 1983-84 Wm. J. Fallon - Chairman, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Program Committee Charles Rehmus - Chairman, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - The Chronicle, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Research Committee 83-84 Mario Bognanno, Chair, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Regional Coordinator Dallas M. Young, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Resignations 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Misc. Letters Folder #1, 1985-1989 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Misc. Letters Folder #2, 1984-1987 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - "Deluxe Check Register" June-July, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Mark Kahn's Article, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Special Committee on Professionalism, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - The Supply of Arbitrators who's making it by Mark L. Kahn, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Future Directions Secretary's Office, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Secretary's Correspondence, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Region #6 - Donald P. Goodman Upstate New York, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Questionnaire (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Saul Wallen Scholarship Fund Cornell University, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Requests for Training Materials, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Request for Permission to Reproduce Articles, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Info. Re arbitration, mediation alternative forms of dispute resolution, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Subcommittee on Research, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Roster: Officers, B/G committee Chairs 1947-1983 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Peterson/Rezler Study, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Postal Costs, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Requests of NAA to Co-Sponsor Meetings, Symposiums, etc., 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - New Member Attendance Annual Meetings 1984-1988 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Tax Deductibility London Trip, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - 1986 Annual Meeting London, 1984-1986 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Liability Insurance - Insurance One, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - "Federal Supplement", 1985 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Krislov/Peck Papers, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Future Directions.Com, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Policy statement - John Dunlop, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Annual Meeting Sites 1947-1986 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Sam Barone, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - China Trip June 1, 1985, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Cleveland Study Group, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Committee Preference Form, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Complaint Against an Arbitrator, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Annual Dues, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Arbitration & Absent employee Block/Mittenthal, 5/84, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Amicus Brief Misco Case, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 55)
- Continuing Education Conference Files, 1983-1986. (Box 8)
  - Seminar Folder #1, 1979-1983 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Seminar Folder #2, 1979-1983 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Board of Governors Meeting October 14-15, 1983 Chicago, Il (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Continuing Education Conference Nov. 11-13, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - NAA Misc. Documents, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Cont. Ed. Conf. Nov 3-4. 1984 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Continuing Education Conference Chicago, Il - Nov. 2-4, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - NAA Cont. Ed. Conference 1985 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - NAA Cont. Ed. Conference 1986 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Cont. Ed. Conference 1985, Minnesota (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - 1984 Cont. Ed. Conference, Illinois (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - NAA - 1986 Meeting (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Office correspondence, (1984) 1985-6; Meeting files, 1990. (Box 9)
  - 85-6 Continuing Education Carlton Snow, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - 85-6 Designating Agency Lia. - Lewis M. Gill, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - 85-6 Dev. Of New Arbitrators Theodore J. St. Antoine, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Executive Committee 1985-6, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - "William J. Fallon", 1984-1986 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Committee Assignments - 85-86, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - 85-6 Overseas Correspondents - Charles J. Morris, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - 85-6 Policy Handbook James C. Duff, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - 85-6 Program Reginald Alleyne, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - 85-6 Pub. Empl. Disputes sett. - Charles M. Rehmus, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - 85-6 Publications - Walter Gershenfeld, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - 85-6 Membership - alfred C. Dybeck, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - 85-6 New Member Orientation - Alexander B. Porter, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Legal Affairs, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Legal Representation - Nathan Lipson, 1984-1986 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - 85-6 1985 Education Conf. John J. Flagler, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - 85-6 Future Meeting Arrange. - nicholas H. Zumas, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - 85-6 academy History - James L. Stern, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - 85-6 Intern Training Charles L. Mullin, Jr., 1986 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Law & Registration Sol M. Yarowski, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - 85-6 Auditing - Howard Cole, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - 85-6 Arr., 1986 Ann. Mtg. - Gershenfelds (Walt & Gladys), 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Archives Anthony V. Sinicorpi, Chair - 86-87, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Memorabiia, 1986-1989 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Archives Correspondence - 1965-1984 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Archives Ret. + Dis Schedule Membership Files, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - NAA Membership Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - NAA - Misc. documents, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    Floppy Disk 3.5 inches
  - NAA Conference - 1991 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - NAA - Conference Sample files: (from previous Confs.), 1986-1989 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Invitation to "Byron R. Abernethy", 1989 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Sol Hammons, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Thomas F. Carey, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Donald P. Goodman, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - NAA - 1991 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Registration Procedures, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Schedule of Events, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Available at Registration Booth, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Printing Information, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Member mailing-Previous Meetings, 1985-1988 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Evaluation Form, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Guest and Intern Confirmation, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Member Confirmation, 1982-1988 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Member Mailing - Philadelphia New Orleans Vancouver, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Registration Packet, 1985-1987 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Guest and Intern Letters, 1986-1988 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Income and Expense Records (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Intern Registration (Sample) (Box 9, Folder 49)
- Meeting files. (Box 11)
  - NAA 43rd Business Meeting (Transcript), 1990 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Dearborn CEC Miscellaneous File, 1989-1990 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - 1990 Education Conference Folder #1 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - 1990 Education Conference Folder #2 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - 1990 Education Conference Folder #3 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - 1990 Education Conference Folder #4 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - 1990 Annual Meeting San Diego (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - 1990 Annual Meeting San Diego Folder #2 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - 1990 Annual Meeting San Diego Folder #3 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Meeting files, 1992. (Box 12)
  - NAA Local Arrangements Committee, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - "Canceled Tickets", 1992 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - NAA Reimbursements, Reciepts, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - "Publisher's", 1992 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - NAA - Arragnements Bank Statements, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - NAA Washington Hilton and Towers, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Denise Clarke, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Washington/ San Diego, 1989-1992 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Guidelines - Atlanta, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Program Committee, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Other NAA Committees, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - "Tony's OFC", 1990-1991 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Entertainment, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Willa R. Moore, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - NAA Member Registrations (and Interns), 1992 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Guest Registration, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - NAA Meetings - 1992 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - 1992 NAA Local Arrangements Committee (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - NAA Dinner Dance, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Meeting files, 1991. (Box 13)
  - Ottawa - New Member Orientation, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - NAA - 1993 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - NAA - Misc. 1991 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Board of Governors Dinner - Sunday, May 26, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Speakers + Comp. Reg, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Workshop Reg., 1991 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - IOE + Beber - Mailings, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - NAA - Committee Reports, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - 1991 - Annual Meeting Arrangements (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - 1991 Annual Meeting - Guest List, 1991-1992 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - 1991 Program (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - 1991 Annual Meeting - Expenses (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Hyatt Regency, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - NAA Annual Meeting 1992 - Registration Fees (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Meeting files. (Box 14)
  - 91 Mid-Year Program - William Holley, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - 91 Mid-Year Arrangements - Claude Foisey, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Board Governors, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - NAA - Finances, Misc. Letters, 1991-1992 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - NAA Executive Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - NAA Committee on Arrangements - 1992 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - '92 Registration, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - NAA - Tyreasurer Documents, 1992-1994 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - '92 Annual Meeting Program and Expenses - Marvin Hill, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - NAA - Annual Meetings Misc., 1991-1992 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Smith-Sternan (insurance file), 1986-1990; Audit reports 1983, 1986-89; 1989 Annual meeting file. (Box 15)
  - Gladys Gershenfeld, 1986-1987 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Arrangements/1989 Ann. Mtg. Arthur A. Malinowski (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Education 1989 Ann. Mtg. - Chicago (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Education 1989 Ann. Mtg. - Chicago (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Continuing Education Confernece, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - 1989 Ann. Mtg. Hotel Agreement Chicago Hilton & Towers (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Program 1989 Annual Meeting "Beber" Helburn, 1988-1989 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - NAA - Financial Reports, Other Reports, 1986-1988 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Photocopies of Checks, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Dallas L. Jones Compensation, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Smith-Sternau Organization, Inc., 1987-1990 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous Inquiries, 1983-1984 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Arthur Stark Arbitrations 1985-1986 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Contested Election - Marvin J. Feldman, 1985-1986 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Deceased members before 7/1/96 A-La. (Box 17)
  - Dr. John R. Abersold, 1954-1975 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Harry Abrahams, 1954-1974 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Robert T. Amis, 1968-1981 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Dr. G. Jay Anyon, 1963-1974 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Orville E. Andrews, 1975-1976 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Walter M. Appleby, 1950-1954 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Otto J. Baab, 1952 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Robert Barlow, 1978-1986 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Marion Beatty, 1956-1967 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Thomas C. Begley, 1953-1954 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Jacob J. Blair, 1954-1976 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Robert O. Boyd, 1952-1979 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Benjamin Franklin Boyer, 1955-1956 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Robert P. Brecht, 1954-1955 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Alfred H. Brent, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Paul F. Brissenden, 1954-1975 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Douglass V. Brown, 1977-1986 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Leo C., S.J. Brown, 1954-1978 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Edward C. Burris, 1955-1977 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Calhoon - Richard P. (Prof.), 1971-1983 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Harry N. Casselman, 1967-1980 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Martin P. Catherwood, 1955-1979 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Nathan Cayton, 1960-1977 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Cyrus Chang, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Andrew V. Clements, 1960-1964 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Alfred A. Cobby, 1951-1962 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - David L. Cole, 1974-1978 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Maxwell Capelot, 1954 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Albert Cornsweet, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Donald A. Crawford, 1956 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Carroll R. Daughtery, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Harold W. Davey, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - William H. Davis, 1954-1957 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Ernest B. De Silva, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Descoteaux, Gaston Professor, 1977-1984 (Box 17, Folder 36)